[Music]
[Laughter]
[Sound of crying]
Hey daughter-in-law, do your work inside the house, open the door quickly, I have to drink,
mother is
empty,
shut up,
listen,
Swami,
even if you tell me [coughing sound]
listen, I can't
see, I am
not working even after the day is full, why don't you
suppress me, why don't you
catch me
[Music]
Hey, listen,
today I am very happy, look at the village
[Music]
Shanti Bhaja Rani Abbas, look today Swami,
listen, say this,
and Rani is in trouble, the
whole village is awakened [Music]
Kali has gone, dengue is coming, today Bindu, listen, look at the
woman, look at the woman, oh
Lord, the
poor
woman's
peacock is coming, the woman is empty, daughter-in-law is at home,
hey,
peace,
look at Baba, do
peace, the
air should feel like heaven, listen, everything is cheap,
everything is not for everyone,
my life is not afraid
[Music]
Hey, Swami, listen, look, there is a tsunami, it's like a chakmak, it's
10 grams, if you
look at it, it's 10 grams, it's like a
tsunami
So I refused and said, you should go to the market and see the
women there, I am also
looking at you
[music] I have
given gifts to the women and
look at all the bags
[music]
Oh no
[laughter] Oh gola gola gola gola gola gola gola no money no
money just give me
peace okay the
ring from the cotton of the
day's hard work the
whole
cycle of the Lord is
going to be the
fair one Oh hey hey hey soul come
hey listen come
[laughter]
[music]